const simpleMathQuestions = [
  {
    question: "10 + 5",
    answer: "15"
  },
  {
    question: "100 / 10",
    answer: "10"
  },
  {
    question: "96 - 6",
    answer: "90"
  },
  {
    question: "10 * 11",
    answer: "110"
  },
  {
    question: "9 * 6",
    answer: "54"
  },
  {
    question: "10 + 25",
    answer: "35"
  },
  {
    question: "25 / 25",
    answer: "1"
  },
  {
    question: "96 - 90",
    answer: "6"
  },
  {
    question: "12 + 11",
    answer: "23"
  },
  {
    question: "5 * 8",
    answer: "40"
  },
  {
    question: "11 + 5",
    answer: "16"
  },
  {
    question: "10 / 2",
    answer: "5"
  },
  {
    question: "10 - 9",
    answer: "1"
  },
  {
    question: "12 * 2",
    answer: "24"
  },
  {
    question: "30 * 2",
    answer: "60"
  },
  {
    question: "10 + 18",
    answer: "28"
  },
  {
    question: "30 / 2",
    answer: "15"
  },
  {
    question: "88 - 8",
    answer: "80"
  },
  {
    question: "5 * 11",
    answer: "55"
  },
  {
    question: "9 * 3",
    answer: "27"
  }
]

export default simpleMathQuestions